Yes, sir.
It's in.
Oh, no.
Here we go.
Thank you very much.
No, I mean, are you okay?
Is it on already?
No, the audio at this stage is...
If it was just sound...
If it was just sound, we wouldn't even know who he is.
Can you speak for a second?
Hello, hello.
Look, I don't know. I don't know who you are.
Who's this low and tall?
It's a balicata.
Oh!
Balikpata. That's nice.
I haven't done that in a while. Not today, I'm sure.
I'm going to make it official...
It's a little bit... well... it's the end of the year.
Christmas balicata.
I don't know what a Christmas barricata is, but I don't understand the ritual, so I'll leave it to you.
It's a balikata. Bon appétit!
Thank you very much. -Barikata is the noodle, isn't it?
Yes, but it depends on the restaurant.
But it depends on the restaurant... some are really homey, some not so much. I order that way too, but...
I often order wire, too, but it's hard and really tough.
It's like baby Star Ramen.
I think it's a straight surface, so it's even thinner than that.
I think it's a straight surface.
I think that's just soaking it a little bit.
Yes, it's just soaked a little, isn't it?
It's just a little bit soaked.
There are people who prefer "kudashirakomi".
I'm sure there are. They commented on it.
I tried it once. It's addictive.
Really? It's really hard!
It's really hard, and it's fresh noodles, so they look raw.
That's great.
I feel a little guilty.
Oh, I see.
I wonder if it's okay to eat it.
Like, "Oh, maybe it's not ready yet." I think that's what the restaurant is trying to get at.
I think that's what the restaurant is trying to do.
Yes, I think so.
For example, you use kanji in your daily life, but when you look at kanji characters, you may think, "I didn't know they were like this...
By the way, there's "centrifugal force", and I think you know the kanji for "balicata".
You understand it, don't you? Yes, I do.
By the way, just a few words... far away... in your mind...
From over there
Yes.
I could have written it if I was asked to, but...
But when I see "centrifugal force" in big letters like this again...
It's a very beautiful word.
I don't know...
This is what it means, isn't it?
Centrifugal force. Centrifugal force, yes.
The power of a distant mind...
It's like someone is thinking about me from afar.
It's a little emo. Centrifugal force is emo, right?
It's an emo feeling.
It's like there's centripetal force or something.
Like, there's centrifugal force.
Centrifugal force is the force of the faraway mind.
That's right.
I see... but I think "centrifugal" means the center.
Centrifugal force is a force far from the center. I like centrifugal force. I'll make it my motto.
Centrifugal force? It's not a motto, it's just something that impressed me.
I was just impressed by it.
We experience centrifugal force frequently. When we drive a car? When you're in a car, you're subjected to centrifugal force.
Like when you're going around a curve. Why so suddenly? It's like a monkey toy. It just started moving.
I was surprised when I felt a contact and it went bang.
I was surprised, but I was told that objects go in a straight line if there's nothing to stop them.
Yes, and you know, for example, when you're on a train or in a car...
For example, when a train starts suddenly, you feel a centrifugal force pulling you backward.
That's the engine force of centrifugal force, or rather, it's another name for the law of completion, which is the law of completion.
I looked it up, and it's easy to understand. I looked up centrifugal force, but it's hard to understand.
It's difficult to understand... but... you know... the hammer throw... it spins around... and the blog moves funny...
You know the hammer throw? You can just throw it.
But you know how they spin around like this and throw it like this?
If it hits a car, it'll be a bullet.
The bullets are dangerous.
That was probably centrifugal force.
No, it was centrifugal force.
That's why it's like this.
Using this kind of force...
That's right.
It's like we're going.
It's making it fly with more momentum.
That's called centrifugal force.
Yes, that's right.
But when you write it in kanji, it's kind of nice, isn't it?
It's nice.
Who is it?
Someone who thinks of me from afar.
That person's power comes to me.
That's the power of a long-distance relationship.
So, people in long-distance relationships always have the power of centrifugal force.
Let's see if we can get a letter from you.
A 8, right?
Yes, yes, a little bit.
I'm offline... in this day and age...
Prodor!
Yes.
Oh, that's it...
That's the corner, isn't it?
The creature's imagination.
It flew!
It flew.
Like Mr. Murobushi?
That's right.
A hammer thrower.
I've been telling you lately... that you need to go.
What amazes me is that Japanese people...
In the old Olympics, they said they weren't good at such feats.
They said they weren't good at it.
I think their physique is a little bit slender compared to western people.
Like a hammer.
But that horror movie she did earlier... her sword is amazing...
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to have a party for a fashion trend, but...
Boo-boo, that's not the right time to say it, right?
Like Cancer couldn't stay.
You're sure he's going to win.
That's why I think the Japanese are changing.
That's right.
Physically, too.
It's a great thing.
Everyone is pretty big these days in Japan.
But it's true that the number of tall people is increasing, isn't it?
The average height is getting taller.
They are getting taller and taller.
Yes, they are. They're strong in soccer, too.
Yes, they are. They're the strongest in Asia.
What? The strongest in Asia!
The strongest in Asia!
They're ranked 15th in the world right now... maybe 15th in Japan?
Amazing! He's strong. I can finally see it.
What?
What's coming into view? Centrifugal force!
What do you see? No. 1? I mean, it's a great achievement to be in the top 10 in the world, in a country.
Maybe the number one is Brazil, or France, or England, or Argentina...
There are 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10 famous countries in the world, and if Japan is among them, this is a great achievement.
What if we go up 5 more? This is still a tough place to make it, but we are strong!
But I would like to see Japan in the top 10, that's for sure.
And then there is the World Cup, you know, soccer.
I don't know if you guys didn't see it, but since we are talking about soccer, Barrigata just kicked a soccer-like kick, right?
It's not soccer at all! It was like a girl kicking a rock because she was sad.
Well, anyway, the World Cup is held once every four years. Just like the Olympics.
I saw the World Cup for the first time in 1980....78 or something.....70 or so years ago.
And for a while after that, there was a period of time when I never thought Japan would make it to the World Cup, like it would never happen.
The J-League was established and the excitement grew, and Japan made its first appearance in the World Cup. However, when we faced the world, we were completely useless. In the beginning. I can't believe that after all these years of frustration, we are now ranked 15th in the world.
I see, that's for sure. So, I don't know how many more years I will live, but while I'm alive, I hope Japan will make it to the top 4 or the finals of the World Cup.
I hope Japan will make it to the top 4 or the final of the World Cup in my lifetime.
If Japan wins the World Cup, I'm sure I'll be able to go to the high heaven without any worries.
I see... but it's possible, isn't it?
I'm not sure if it's going to be next year or the year after next.
Next year... next year... next year... more water... more water... the other day... it was amazing...
No, no, no, centrifugal force has nothing to do with it.
I didn't see it, but here it is... Spain and Germany were in the same group... and nobody expected them to win.
And nobody expected them to win.
Everyone in the world thought Spain and Germany would win, and they beat them both.
And then the whole world was surprised and said, "Japan is really strong!
I'm in such a situation right now... I understand that without remembering it properly... I'll take the exam...
I'm going to take the exam so I'm going to clear up soccer
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get the information you need.
I've emailed you to contribute to the "Creature Creation" section.
Black Mumber.
Black Mamba Brah!
It's not "Bamboo Bagger" Takeshi, it's "Black Mamba" Takeshi, and I'm drunk on "Black Mamba" Takeshi.
I'm drunk on Mr. Takeshi!
Black Mamba is the best part of Black Mamba, isn't it?
I think it's a song, but it's a real song.
Pop Pop Pop, I think.
I think it was a pop-pop song...
The first letter of Bludge is "Black Mambur." Black Mambur.
I think it's a bit more than that.
Black Mokka
That's so cute.
I'll hit a home run no matter what the pitch.
That's right. I can't protect him anymore.
It's going into the stands. That's right.
It won't reach us.
So, while you were writing...
I have an announcement... for the upcoming Devil Festival...
This year, too.
We'll be giving away various illustrations that we've drawn... in our own handwriting... again this year.
I'm going to give away some of them.
I'm sure it's the original, but it's nostalgic...
We'll be handing out triangles to those who come to the Devil Festival on the day of the event.
The lucky winner will get a one-of-a-kind illustrated flip book drawn by a regular Devil in the museum.
The winner will receive a one-of-a-kind illustrated flip book that was written by a regular Devil in the Museum on the show.
So, I think it was before, but I don't know what it's about, but it's not a creature, it's not a living thing.
I don't understand why they're so mysterious.
I'm sure that the people who do the booby trap remember the pictures that you drew.
I don't know... but... you're looking at this...
I'm sure you'll enjoy it too... and I hope you'll do the reveal too.
I'd like you to put in a special mention of Mr. Ippo's drawing today.
I'm sorry to bother you, but I'm sure you'll all enjoy this.
He's a good boy.
Bookman! Blackman!
Boo-hoo!
Boo-boo!
It's almost finished.
Almost there. It's kind of a cool name, isn't it?
Black Mambur. That's for sure.
It's like Black Thunder.
Black Mamba. Here we go.
You two have been writing a lot.
Here we go. Here we go.
You don't have to do that.
Oh!
That's terrible.
You're wasting your time.
The length
That's terrible!
So...
Well, first of all...
Let's go to the doctor.
Let's go.
This way, sir.
Bang.
Ha-ha-ha-ha. What?
What?
What the hell? Why are you leaning?
Why this lotus, Mr. Takeichi?
Are you thinking of Takeichi? I'm a little...
Did I get pulled in? I've been pulled.
Oh, my God!
I wonder what this is.
It's over 1,000, right?
It's breaking through the limit.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What is it? What is it?
It's a cat, right?
It's not a cat? No, no, no. What? What?
A cat?
Hail. Hail? Hail? Pitch-black hail.
I think it's pitch-black hail.
I see. I thought so too. A pitch-black hail?
A man in black tights wearing a cat's headdress, like this.
Black Mamba, Black Mamba, Black Mamba, Black Mamba...
I imagined him dancing.
Maybe it's a rehearsal for the Shiki Theater Company. A rehearsal.
The Lion King, the one from Cats, the one from Cats.
Okay, so we're going to do Japanica.
I'm back!
I'm sure he'll explain to you what's going on.
Calm down, calm down, calm down, calm down, everyone.
Calm down, please.
Mantis?
This is...
This is a hand and this is a sense of touch?
Tentacles.
Do you have one like a praying mantis?
Yes, I do.
That's a sickle, not a thing on your head.
Yes, it is.
Hand-like.
I see.
That doesn't make sense.
It doesn't make sense.
I'll just add something else.
It's got a mantis.
It's a praying mantis.
If it's a mantis, what's this thing on its head?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
A praying mantis. You mean a black praying mantis?
Yes, yes... yes... yes...
I see... I see...
Mantis... like a mamba.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
I see... a famous major a.k.a. Mambalan...
I'm afraid of both of them.
I'm afraid of both of them... they look like they've been around for a long time.
It's scary when it's painted black... it's like it has a grudge...
It's a little scary.
By the way, Black Mumber...
It's a snake!
This is...
It's a very poisonous snake.
What's more...
It's dripping with venom.
I think I've got it.
I have it.
I wanted to make it look like a poisonous snake.
Or maybe it's actually coming out.
I don't know.
But at first glance.
I think, "Oh my God.
Is it pitch black?
It's not pitch black.
Gray.
It's not black, it's a little grayish, but I guess it's okay to call it black.
The orange guy...
I read on wikipedia about the ecology of these snakes.
Vipers are mainly venomous, but they're all poisonous, but they're properly envenomated.
They bite a lot, but they don't have the energy to release their venom.
It's hard to produce venom, isn't it?
That's right.
So there are those who can get rid of the venom, and those who can't do it anymore, so they release all the venom they bite.
Dr. Manba releases all of them.
He's very aggressive.
And, you know, removing the poison is a cool word.
I wonder...
"Bite.
Like, "Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye." Like, "Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye.
It's like... a little... a little... a little... a little... a little... a little... a little... a little... a little... a little... a little... a little.
Let's look up "snake venom remover"...
most of the people who watch it like poisonous snakes.
I'm sure most of the people who watch the show like poisonous snakes.
I mean the kind of snakes that don't emit venom.
The Black Mamba's name comes from the black inside of its mouth.
I'm sure everyone loves vipers.
I'm sure there's someone out there who's winning...
I'm sure it's like I'm off every time.
I've seen it every time I'm offline... and it's called a dry bite...
That's why I can't do the Black Mamba Dry Bite.
I'll take it out... from the car in general.
Dry bite...
Mr. Pom-Pom.
I love them... and I love them... and I love them... and I love them... and I love them.
I love it!
I've never been bitten by a booboo before, have you?
But I'm a human being... and I'm afraid of poison... but it's the other side that scares me the most.
So he bites you?
That's how most wild animals attack humans.
So we're stronger than them?
I don't know.
I don't know... but when I look at it from an animal's point of view, standing on two legs...
It's kind of scary, isn't it?
It's a little scary, isn't it?
It's not the same thing as dancing...
So, we'll continue with the creature creation...
If you have any ideas for creatures, please send them to us.
If you have any living creatures, please send them to us.
So... a little more... a little more goodies for all of you who are watching the story.
I've explained everything to you.
Let's start with this.
Here's a Ka na de Biru towel.
It's just an ordinary towel.
I don't need to explain this any more... I don't need to explain this any more...
This is a bowl of rice from the old days, and it looks just like this
If you eat a little ramen, it tastes good... it's the opposite... the cooperation is the opposite, isn't it?
You can't see it, you can't see it, you can't see it, you can't see it, you can't see it.
I think you all know what I'm talking about.
I'm sure you all know what I'm talking about.
Bulger, may I have you put this on your arm?
Yes, sir.
And if you press it a little bit...
There's a click somewhere.
Here...
It glows.
Here.
It lights up in the dark.
It hides everything.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, well, we have the mist band, and as you can see, we also have this kind of an actor's band, but we also have this kind of an actor's band, but we also have this kind of an actor's band.
This is her own Akusta.
This is a very simple one, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
The Balicata series is amazing, you know...
You know, the big kanbachi type...
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
And isn't this the best one?
Yes, indeed!
It's a quote...
Trekker.
Well, I guess that's it.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's the way to split it.
Cicadas are by far the worst.
If you cut it out this much, it makes you look like a bad person.
What's this? Air Max hunting?
What's an Air Max hunt?
It's called hunting Air Max.
I'll tell you what...
I'll start from the beginning.
Nike.
Nike?
Nike's Air Max was first released in the 1990s.
When they first came out, they were in short supply and very popular.
What kind of line is that?
I remember now... that's not a quote from me... Yamatsukari... yes... yes... well... this is how it was made during that period.
The first thing that comes to mind is the fact that the first time you see a new product, you're going to want to know what it is.
I'd like to invite you all to Bill Festivo next February 23rd, and I'd appreciate it if you could attend and participate.
I'd appreciate it if you could invite everyone to Bill Festivo and give me some love.
And then it'll be over and done with...
I can't buy it anymore.
If you can't buy it, you can't buy it.
There's no such thing as centrifugal force anymore
So, I'll just go on like this, huh?
Next week, we'll be broadcasting live again at 8:00.
We'll be talking about snakes again next week because you love snakes!
Poisonous snakes!
We all know a lot about snakes.
You know, poisonous snakes are really interesting.
I don't want to get bitten by one, but...
But you know what they're like.
Venomous creatures... are just so...
It's a beautiful thing, the way it lives.
I see.
8 is like that too... you know... once you hit it, the needle falls out... and it's useless... you know... it's like a one-hit kill.
I'm going to do it again next week because it's so interesting.
But there are some people who don't like it... who think it's funny... like "Screw you, don't play heavy, don't play with me!
I'm not going to watch any more TV shows. They're too heavy.
I don't think so, but I'll see you next week at 8:00 p.m.
Thank you very much for watching this week!
I don't know how to cure tinnitus.